Loot a hello
hello friends I am your friend Lagan se
ok we are Pun Motors you are very welcome to this world of Pun Motors
today I am going to
show you budget SUV
is the most demanding vehicle and this is a special vehicle so
this vehicle is a bomb acid bomb vehicle
so let's clean this blog and if
you have not subscribed to our channel yet then do it
and in such a situation women will keep
getting the latest notifications so
let's show you so do it
hello friends today we are going to have
Mahindra XUV 500 w8 Yogi automatic
transmission
that in the entire budget such a disease comes that Mahindra is the
best selling vehicle this is the
vehicle at today's time and how did
we have this vehicle because this vehicle
is Embassy alliance if we talk about the details of the vehicle it is
2016 model it is a December minded vehicle married
human only 40,000 is the vehicle and
w8 yogi to undo is automatic inside and the
vehicle bumper-to-bumper scratch less single
pin is inside the vehicle it is a basic
Dhundhari because it is such a well
maintained vehicle  It is so that's why the car
is special, let me ask you about the car,
this is our soil's batting and the
most attractive green, Sikander has
a projector lens, and this is
my phone glamour car, which is
quite bulky of Kallu and is for work, I
ask him to take it with him, those people come
inside the car, now let's talk about other things,
inside the parlor debit card, for that car
you took only 400 rupees and you
can see the tyre of the car, you can update the car want to
2016 data, the car is given ghee, look,
even after 40,000 runs, the car's fast
looks like this today, you have new goals, the
car runs in the message, it
runs very normal sugar, there are so many
cameras installed there, so many hard
fast trains run there, the car and the plane of
Hindu, so the car has run accordingly, it is
maintained like that, if we talk about the body
lines, then the body lines will
get a single drinking water and it is totally a
completely interior car, bumper-to-bumper,
why  The bandwagon is
that here the
new Delhi and automatic transmission of the vehicles
show the control system,
all its settings are made normal,
I am safe and not just of the settings,
I sit in the bathroom and solve
that foreign ji last, then you have not used it yet, do it, do it, the
glass holders inside Amresh's car
in the center,
people of this car, see, then I fell in love, there is
no single express inside the car, so
again and again just set it, that the car is
really a car in itself, it is a diamond, it is a
pizza bread, that car,
a person in the batting of a woman,
120 500, a car, 20w debit translation
for a case of fraud, it is
simple, by worshipping it from here, the desired
result will be achieved, the unfaithful
office is inside it
and here it does not have Stephanie Swift,
it is simple, if we open it,
it will be typed and Richa,
I have also done it inside the light ji to see,
Ajay,
I have Suresh's very unique made mouth, how to
mirror for this, where is it, it is a
symbolic thing  Anup, the mayor of the city lives in our
side mirror,
you talk about the fact that there are going to be a lot of vehicles in Kunj Motor,
I will discuss the details with you once again, it is
2016, Vishambar is the minister, MS Word is human, the
vehicle is
torn, Arun is driving, the owner is first, the
vehicle is bumper-to-bumper, enters Edison,
male member, insurance is tyre, Karni, if you
see, almost brand, it is important,
even after driving, the
price of the vehicle, the arm spinner, Ram Lakhan is
cleaning it now, the rest of the rotis will
get a discount, so come quickly, give this Guru
Graha and like the drinks, thank
you, thank you,
Jhal.